{ "categories":
    [ { "name": "Standards of living and water sources",
        "answers":
         [ { "question": "What is your housing status of ownership?",
             "answer": 0 },
           { "question": "What are your sources of potable water?",
             "answer": [ 0, 1 ] },
           { "question": "What are the sources of your secondary sources?",
             "answer": [ 1, 2, 4 ] },
           { "question": "What are you using the potable water supply for? (Check as much as possible)",
             "answer": [ 1, 3, 4 ] },
           { "question": "What are you using the secondary water supply for?",
             "answer": [ 0, 2, 4 ] } ] },
      { "name": "Health, Sanitation and Hygiene",
        "answers":
         [ { "question": "What is your housing status of ownership?",
             "answer": [ 0, 1 ] },
           { "question": "Are there any members of the family diagnosed with waterborne diseases such as:",
             "answer": [ 0, 3 ] },
           { "question": "Which of the following practices prevent waterborne related diseases?",
             "answer": [ 1, 2, 4 ] },
           { "question": "Do you have toilet facility?", "answer": 0 },
           { "question": "If yes, what type of toilet facility it is?",
             "answer": [ 2, 4, 1 ] },
           { "question": "If no, where do you urinate/defecate?",
             "answer": [ 1, 2, 0 ] },
           { "question": "Do you have a pet?", "answer": 0 },
           { "question": "Where does your pet litter?", "answer": [ 0, 1, 2 ] },
           { "question": "Have you done the following activities in the river?",
             "answer": [ 2, 4, 1 ] } ] },
      { "name": "Ecological Sanitation",
        "answers":
         [ { "question": "What is your housing status of ownership?",
             "answer": [ 1, 3, 2, 0, 4 ] },
           { "question": "Do you have a garden or agricultural land?",
             "answer": 0 },
           { "question": "If yes, do you use a fertilizer?", "answer": 0 },
           { "question": "What kind of fertlizer do you use?", "answer": 0 },
           { "question": "Do you have livestock/s?", "answer": 0 },
           { "question": "If yes, what kind of livestock/s?",
             "answer": [ 0, 1 ] },
           { "question": "How do you manage livestock manure?",
             "answer": [ 1, 2, 4 ]
           }
         ]
      }
    ]
}
